A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Audio-Visual and Oversized Materials, 7
  - Tapes and CD (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Zip disk, "Peptide and Protein 4.3 Photos by Module", 2016:FA415:015 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Zip disk, "Peptide and Protein 4.3 Photos by Module", 2016:FA415:016 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Zip disk, "RBM Slides, RNase, Chinese Scientists", 2016:FA415:017 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Zip disk, "RNase Illustrations, Continuous Flow Diagrams", 2016:FA415:018 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - CD, "Peptides and Proteins 4.3 Graphics and Photos", 2016:FA415:019 (Box 411, Folder 2626)